{
    "subject": "resource/Sumeet_Raghavan",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Actor",
    "human_readable": "Sumeet Raghavan is an actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9834544658660889,
            "question": "Is Sumeet Raghavan a famous actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9217053055763245,
            "question": "In which films or TV shows has Sumeet Raghavan starred?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9188143014907837,
            "question": "What are some of Sumeet Raghavan's notable roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9098061919212341,
            "question": "Has Sumeet Raghavan appeared in movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8175422549247742,
            "question": "Is Sumeet Raghavan a well-known figure in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7781991362571716,
            "question": "What profession does Sumeet Raghavan have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479298710823059,
            "question": "Is Sumeet Raghavan a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6358129382133484,
            "question": "What kind of work is Sumeet Raghavan known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6227776408195496,
            "question": "What is Sumeet Raghavan's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5397824048995972,
            "question": "Does Sumeet Raghavan act on stage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sumeet Raghavan is an actor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8495_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sumeet Raghavan's area of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8495_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work is Sumeet Raghavan known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8495_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sumeet Raghavan a musician?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8495_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8495_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the value as \"yes\" or \"no\":\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Sumeet Raghavan is indeed an actor, with mentions of his roles in various TV series and movies, such as Wagle Ki Duniya - Nayi Peedi Naye Kissey, Hudd Kar Di, Sarabhai vs Sarabhai, etc."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly indicate that Sumeet Raghavan is indeed an actor, mentioning his roles in multiple films and television series."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}